你父親有一位特別伴侶
Your father has a special someone.
我們得在這里賺點錢
We gotta make money off this place.
-怎么賺  -建一座劇院
- By doing what? - What about...
怎么樣
a theater?
出柜了啊
The closet door opened.
他說他要搬到圣何塞
He says he's moving to San Jose;
她則說要搬到恩西諾市
she says she's moving to Encino.
我得選擇我要跟誰生活
I'm supposed to pick where I wanna go.
我們要建一座露天劇院
We're building an amphitheater.
現在我開始感興趣了
Now this I'm interested in.
-真的嗎  -成為露天劇場的合伙人
- You're interested in? - Partnering.
-誰給你買的花盆  -你在這兒干嘛
- Who gave you flowerpots? - What are you doing here?
這是我哥史考特  史考特  這是戈多
This is my brother Scotty. Scotty, this is Godot.
你好  年輕人
Well hello, young man.
順便說一下  薩莎也翹課了
Sasha's awol too by the way.
我知道她在哪里
Well, I know where she is.
她在找公寓  并且已經找到一間了
Apartment hunting. And she found one.
好了  女生們
All right, ladies.
保持輕盈  注意間距
Keep it light, watch your spacing.
舞步整齊
Dance as one.
我在考慮留劉海
I'm thinking of getting bangs.
真的嗎
Oh yeah?
改變一下形象  你覺得如何
Something different. What do you think?
你想要做點改變嗎
You need a change?
是啊
Well, yeah.
難道你的生活很無聊
Your life is boring?
-金妮  -而且你的朋友也很無聊
- Ginny-- - Your friends are boring?
天啊
Oh boy.
新生活  新朋友
New life, new friends,
新劉海
New bangs.
女生們  多動腳  少動嘴
Moving the feet, not the mouths, ladies.
金妮  拜托  別再提柯澤特了
Ginny please, get over this Cozette thing.
對不起  沒和你說我去練輪滑
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about roller derby,
但我也沒告訴其他人
but I didn't tell anyone.
既沒告訴我爸媽  也沒告訴我哥哥
Not my parents or my brother.
你哥哥
Your brother?
-我是說...  -你沒告訴查理嗎
- I just mean-- - You didn't tell Charlie?
可是你和他那么的親密
But you're so close with him.
你什么都對查理講
You tell Charlie everything.
-我只是...  -我不知道你沒告訴查理
- I was just-- - I didn't know you didn't tell Charlie.
如果你沒告訴查理
If you didn't tell Charlie,
很顯然  是我反應過度了
then clearly, I'm overreacting.
是這樣嗎
Aren't I?
我反應過度了嗎
Aren't I overreacting?
波  沒有正確答案的
There's no good answer, Boo.
比方說你的閨蜜  在你不知情的情況下
Say your best friend suddenly had a secret life
有了全新的生活
that you didn't know about.
你發現后
When you found out,
會感到憤怒  覺得被背叛嗎
would you feel mad, betrayed?
就像是你最好的朋友
Like maybe your best friend wasn't actually
根本不是你最好的朋友
your best friend at all?
-好吧  -或者...
- Well-- - Or...
一旦你發現她也沒有告訴她哥哥
once you found out she didn't tell her brother either,
你會舒服點  然后對此釋懷嗎
would you feel fine and forget it ever happened?
-我不懂你的意思  -什么
- I missed you. - What?
默默不語的雙唇才是動人的雙唇
A closed mouth is a pretty mouth.
-對不起  -隨便吧
- Sorry. - Whatever.
我就和她說過兩次話
I talked to her twice.
并不代表我們就是最好的朋友
It's not like we're best friends.
-她給你取了外號  -拜托
- She named you. - Come on.
無敵破壞王克里奧
Cleo-Smacktra?
她得耗費了多少心力
How many seconds of thought
才能想出來啊
did she put into that one?
你們又吵架啦
Are you guys fighting again?
不知道  關于這段關系
I don't know. I am the last one
我是唯一一個被蒙在鼓里的
to know anything in this relationship.
難以置信  我只不過離開了五分鐘
Unbelievable. I turn my back for five minutes.
柯澤特和我只是碰巧在旱冰場遇到
Cozette just happened to be at the rink when I was there.
我又沒有打電話給她  然后說
It's not like I called her up and said
"我要告訴你所有的秘密  柯澤特"
"I'll tell you all my secrets, Cozette."
我不想再聽到任何"柯"的諧音
I don't want to hear the c-word anymore.
當然  科澤特就在我右邊
Of course, right to Cozette.
那是舞蹈編排而已
That's the choreography.
她也許向范妮夫人施了魔法
She probably cast some kind of spell on Madame Fanny
把編舞弄成這樣
to make it happen like that.
柯澤特無所不能  柯澤特是女巫
Cozette can do anything. Cozette's a wizard.
我以為你不想聽到任何"柯"的諧音
I thought you didn't want to hear the c-word?
我對金妮的事感到抱歉
I'm sorry about Ginny.
我愛她  但是她太頑固了
I love her, but she's stubborn.
給她點時間吧
Just give her time.
你沒做錯任何事
You didn't do anything wrong.
誰是金妮
Who's Ginny?
她有魔力  又完美
She's magic and perfect,
從大眾眼光看  她還無比時髦
and worldly, and so so hip.
倫敦的一條街道  以時裝出名
她就是穿著芭蕾舞鞋的卡納比街
She's Carnaby Street in pointe shoes.
我們什么時候見過柯澤特啦
When did we even meet Cozette?
我就是柯澤特
I'm Cozette.
多么精彩的初次彩排啊
What a wonderful first try.
它讓我想起我青年時光
It reminds me of a time
芭蕾舞劇  許多芭蕾舞團的保留劇目
那時我在《仙女們》擔任獨舞演員
when I was a young soloist in "Les Sylphides"
我和一位舞者大吵一架
and I was having a terrible fight
她扮演了一位仙女...
with a nymph--
更貼切的說  是仙女花癡
or a nympho, which is a more accurate description
這也是我們吵架的真正原因
and the actual reason for our fight.
總之  彩排過程中我們破口大罵
Anyhow we wound up having words during rehearsal.
你們知道后來怎么樣了嗎
And do you know what happened?
首演當晚  我們只能在大廳的貨攤邊
We both watched opening night
看別人表演
from the concession stand in the lobby.
請記住這一點...
So with that in mind...
心 舞
第一季第15集
我忘記了
Oh, I forgot.
我帶了購物袋
I brought my own bags.
別磨蹭了
Let's go.
你開什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding.
-你們能再開個收款通道嗎  -拜托
- Could you guys open up another register? - Come on!
快點啊
Come on.
那就是舞臺
And that's the stage
米利森特·斯通藝術表演中心即將落成
周圍會擺滿座位
with seating all around.
我們還打算在樹上
Oh, and we're going to hang lanterns
掛滿燈籠
in all the trees.
演出前它們會被點亮
They'll be dimmed before the performances.
很漂亮  不是說你  索爾
Pretty. No, not you, Saul.
我怎么會說你漂亮呢
Why would I call you pretty?
希望舞臺夠大
I hope the stage is big enough.
你覺得舞臺夠大了嗎
Do you think the stage is big enough?
針對中場秀還是...
For the halftime show, or?
美國超級碗的中場表演  場面盛大
你說得對  說得對  當我沒問
You're right. You're right. It's fine.
如果你想要更大的舞臺
Whoa, hey. If you need a bigger stage,
那我們就做一個唄
let's make a bigger stage.
他們遲交兩周的房租了
They're two weeks late on rent.
找個會說立陶宛語的無賴
Go find someone that speaks Lithuanian deadbeat
把他們趕出去
and tell them to get out.
-我好激動啊  -我知道
- I am so excited. - I know.
你討厭我身上的這件上衣
I'm wearing that shirt you hate
你竟然沒問我是怎樣卑躬屈膝才買到它
and you haven't asked me what bum I had to roll to get it yet.
你們覺得舞臺怎樣
What do you girls think of the stage?
太酷了
It's really cool.
我還沒在戶外跳過舞呢
I've never danced outside before.
如果想要更大的舞臺
If the stage is gonna be bigger,
我們得跟胖子鮑勃和瘦子唐說說
we have to tell fat Bob and skinny Don.
我跟他們發誓說一切就緒了
And I swore to them that we'd finalized everything.
他們不會開心的
This will not make them happy.
女士  我們不是來討他們歡心的
Ladies, we are not here to make them happy.
這是為了我們和那些孩子
This is for us and the kids.
嘿  胖子鮑勃和瘦子唐
Hey! Fat Bob and skinny Don.
我們一般不當著他們的面叫他們綽號
Oh, we don't usually call them that to their face.
-有問題嗎  -我們想擴建舞臺
- Is something wrong? - We want to make the stage bigger.
他們想擴建舞臺
They want to make the stage bigger.
我們已經訂好了木材
We already ordered the wood.
上周就訂了
Last week.
打了電話  開了支票
Made the call, wrote the check.
你能再多訂點嗎
Well, can you order more,
還是說木頭被你們訂光了
or is that the last wood in the world?
是啊  這個諷刺可不夠高明
Uh, yeah, the sarcasm has not gone unnoticed.
但你得知道  這么做會拖慢進度
But see, now, there's gonna be some lag time.
-二  三  -四  五
- Two, three... - Four, five...
-周  -月
- Weeks. - Months.
-月  -得了吧
- Months? - Come on.
給我最終期限  胖子鮑勃和瘦子唐
Give me the bottom line here, fat Bob and skinny Don.
天啊  好吧
Oh, jeez, well--
借口留著編給斯皮爾伯格聽  奧利維耶
Save it for Spielberg, Olivier.
斯皮爾伯格  美國著名電影導演
-給個天數  -十天
- Give me the number. - 10.
-十天  -成交
- 10? - Done.
你知道  一個更大的舞臺
And you know, a bigger stage
需要更多的燈
is gonna need more lights.
-沒問題  -意味著兩張
- Fine. - That means two...
-三張  -四張額外的支票
- Three... - Four extra banks.
-做吧  -等等  米利
- Do it. - Wait, Milly,
這樣太過了  我們不需要更多的燈
That's too much. We don't need more lights.
對啊  把那些丑孩子往暗處推就行了
Yeah, we'll just shove the ugly kids in the dark spots.
多點燈光會讓舞臺更漂亮
More lights will make it beautiful.
舞臺必須漂亮
It has to be beautiful.
芭蕾舞中的一切都是漂亮的
Everything is beautiful at the ballet.
你們敲詐完了嗎
You done fleecing me yet?
-還沒吧  -建點東西去
- Probably not. - Go build something.
好吧  如果他們還在嘰歪抱怨
Well, if we're getting noise complaints
告訴他們從十點到六點
tell them they can't run their heart-lung machine
休想用人工心肺機
between 10:00 and 6:00.
米歇爾  我不得不說
Michelle, I have to say
讓米利參與其中
it was a stroke of genius getting Milly
真是天才之舉
involved with this.
謝謝
Wow, thanks.
那件襯衫把你襯得像高速公路隧道
And that shirt makes you look like a freeway underpass.
再跟我說一遍總盈利
Tell me again the total profit after expenses.
再說一遍
Tell me again.
我愛死錢了
I love money.
等我給你們開好支票
Let me just get you those checks
我就離開
and I'll get out of your hair.
還需要別的東西嗎
Is there anything else we need?
沒了  你真是我們的天使  米利
Oh, no. You've been an absolute godsend, Milly.
真的  你做的每件事
Really. Everything you've done has been
幾乎完美
just about perfect.
幾乎
Just about?
什么叫"幾乎"
What do you mean "Just about"?
不  是絕對完美
No. Absolutely perfect.
父母們做的衣服一定可愛極了
The costumes the parents are making are going to be lovely.
甚至還有一些是專業級的
We won't even miss the professionally made ones.
我們還沒有服裝
Shouldn't we have those?
在完美的世界里是有的
Well, in a perfect world.
我活的世界必須完美
I live in a perfect world.
這沒什么關系的
I think we'll be fine.
聽著  如果我把這些錢都投在劇院
Look, if I spend all this money on a theater
然后舞者表演得像
and then the dancers show up looking like
音樂劇《霧都孤兒》的鄉村巡回演出
a bus and truck tour of "Oliver",
根據狄更斯的小說《霧都孤兒》改編而成的音樂劇
還不如把錢投在公共電視
I might as well be investing in public television.
-去訂服裝  -你確定嗎
- Order the costumes. - Are you sure?
確定
I am positive.
你不會后悔的
You won't be sorry.
那些漂亮的衣服會讓
These beautiful costumes will put those
引座員的二手制服黯然失色
secondhand usher outfits to shame.
太邪惡了
So evil.
引座員  我們有引座員嗎
Ushers. Do we have those?
你說得對  我們不需要他們
Oh, you're right. We don't need them.
太聰明了  看到沒  米歇爾
Smart. You see, Michelle?
這就是你需要商業合伙人的原因
This is what you have a business partner for.
她會告訴你如何削減成本
To tell you exactly where to cut the costs.
不要引座員
No ushers.
等下  我想要引座員
Wait, I want ushers.
-或許明年  -今年
- Well, maybe next year. - This year.
六個月后再考慮
Let's give it six months.
現在  現在就要  多少合適呢
Now, I want them now. How many?
-10人  -20人
- 10? - 20.
20名引座員  都是男生
20 ushers, all boys.
個子高  體型美  去招聘吧
Tall, built, find them.
我是斯通
Stone here.
盧克神父  感謝回電
Father Luke, thanks for calling me back.
我理解在您的宗教傳統中
I understand your religious tradition
需要掛很多飾品
calls for hanging a lot of paraphernalia,
但它毀了我的
but it's destroying my walls.
每個耶穌受難像都要釘三個釘子
I mean, it's three nails for every crucifix.
簡直是我在受難
You're killing me.
-我們還好嗎  -很好
- We good? - We're perfect.
而且邪惡
And evil.
拜拜  米利
Good-bye, Milly.
服裝  引座員制服
Costumes, usher uniforms,
引座員
ushers.
我們需要那些東西
We need all those things.
我只是在想
I'm just wondering,
你真的打算訂做全部服裝么
are you putting out for all of this?
畢竟有許多東西
'Cause there's definitely some sort of
還可以發揮余熱呢
quid pro quo going on here.
別這么庸俗
Don't be vulgar.
我這么做都是為了藝術
I'm doing it for the art.
還有孩子們
And for the children.
我對此沒什么意見
Hey, I'm not judging.
反正一切開銷由她支付
As long as the lady's paying for it,
為什么不用駱馬毛服裝呢
why not take the vicuna?
好了  我們開始
All right, let's begin.
一位  蹲
First position, plies.
-雨衣  -帶上
- Raincoat? - Bring it!
-比基尼  -帶上
- Bikini? - Bring it.
-牛仔睡褲  -帶上
- Pajama jeans? - Bring them.
-手銬  -扔進去
- Handcuffs? - Toss them in.
安全帽  烤盤  香蕉女郎唱片集
Hard hat, waffle iron, Bananarama box set?
上世紀八十年代英國著名的音樂組合
干嘛要帶上烤盤
What the hell are we gonna do with a waffle iron?
得了吧  史考特  告訴我你要干嘛
Scotty, come on. Tell me what this thing is.
這是我的最后一夜
Hey, it's my last night.
傳統上  將要度過最后一夜的人
And the rules are whoever has the last night
可以選擇任意狂歡活動
gets to choose the last night blowout activity.
-別小看傳統  -我想知道細節
- Don't flout the rules. - But I need details.
我告訴過你  是在沙漠里
I told you, it's in the desert.
-就像燒人節  -這什么也說明不了
- It's like Burning Man. - Which means nothing.
由一個名為"Black Rock City  LLC"的組織發起的反傳統狂歡節
-你聽說過燒人節  -我聽說過
- You've heard of Burning Man. - Yes, I've heard of Burning Man,
但鑒于我從未參加過
but since I've never been to Burning Man,
我只能猜測發生了什么
I can only guess what takes place.
比如他們是不是真的燒了一個人
Like do they really burn a man?
這個人是誰  他很討人厭嗎
And who is this man? Is he annoying?
-他是罪有應得嗎  -你得自己找出答案
- Does he have it coming? - You'll just have to find out.
至少回答我這個問題
Okay, well at least answer me this.
我們到了之后  有廁所嗎
When we get there, will there be a bathroom?
定義一下"廁所"
Define bathroom.
見到你很高興
Nice seein' ya.
到家給我電話
Call me when you get home.
拜托  你去拜訪我時
Oh, come on. Did I complain
逼著我去變裝舞會  我有抱怨過嗎
when you visited me and made me go see drag queen bingo?
抱怨得十分激烈
Vehemently.
它太可怕了  害我迷路了
'Cause it was horrible and I lost.
搞笑極了
Yeah, that was fun.
來吧  這個也很有趣
Well, come on, this will be fun too.
拜托  這就像我們小時候的
Come on, it'll be like all those cool road trips
那些很棒的公路旅行
we took as kids.
什么很棒的公路旅行
What cool road trips?
你忘了  大峽谷
What do you mean? The Grand Canyon,
新奧爾良  太陽錄音室
New Orleans, Sun Studios,
大煙山
the Smoky Mountains.
-假的  - 大煙山是假的嗎
- Fake. - The Smoky Mountains are fake?
旅行是假的
The trips were fake.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
媽媽以前常帶我們去假旅行
Mom used to take us on fake trips.
-你不知道嗎  -不知道
- You didn't know that? - No.
深夜里她把我們放進車里
She'd put us in the car really late at night,
帶我們在周圍轉幾個小時
and then drive us around for hours
直到我們睡著  等我們醒了
until we fell asleep. And then when we woke up,
她使我們相信
she'd convince us that
我們經歷了一次有趣的冒險
we just had a really fun adventure.
不  這不可能
No. That's impossible.
我還記得乘熱氣球
I remember that thing with the balloons.
-從未發生過  -才怪
- Never happened. - Yes.
很多個巨大的  掛著綢帶的
There were like these huge red balloons
紅色熱氣球
with ribbons hanging down.
-確實沒有發生過  -風揚起
- I'm afraid not. - The wind kicked up
我們握著綢帶  乘著熱氣球
and we held the ribbons and we rode on them?
-沒有熱氣球嗎  -她騙我們的
- No balloons? - She gaslighted us, dude.
這是我第二喜歡的童年記憶
That was my second favorite childhood memory.
唐·麥克林沒在你十五歲的生日派對上表演
Don Mclean didn't play your fifth birthday party.
美國游吟歌手
你自己靜一下吧
I'll give you some space.
我剛搬進去  需要電啟動電器
I just moved in so I need to get the power turned on.
明天就能來電  很好
By tomorrow would be great actually.
信用卡  我有
A credit card? Well, I do.
其實是我父母的
I mean, it's technically my parents',
不過在商店里可以刷  所以...
But they take it at the mall, so...
我們能跳過存款這塊嗎
Can we just skip the deposit?
我很有責任心
I'm very responsible.
這是真的  她從未醉過或懷孕過
It's true. She's never been drunk or pregnant.
我能用現金結算嗎
Look, can I just give you cash?
我想自動取款機
Oh. I don't think the ATM
不會讓我一次取那么多錢
will give me that much.
真的嗎
Really?
我以前從未去過銀行
Wow, I've never actually gone inside a bank before.
是的  這將是一次冒險
Yes. It will be an adventure.
謝謝
Thank you.
有人知道哪兒有銀行嗎
Anyone know where a bank is?
這么多的待辦事項
That is a very long to-do list.
電視  電話  網絡  供電...
Cable, phone, internet, electricity...
-煤氣呢  -怎么了
- What about gas? - What about it?
你的熱水器是電熱的還是煤氣的
Is your water heater electric or gas?
-我不知道  -很可能是煤氣的
- I have no idea. - It's probably gas.
打電話給煤氣公司
Calling the gas company.
工程浩大啊
This is a lot of work.
但超值的  公寓太棒了
But it's worth it. The apartment is awesome.
就需要一點小裝修
I mean, it needed a little jeuje.
刷刷棳  裝個新水槽
A paint job, new sink,
我撤掉了地毯
I'm pulling up the carpets.
那些裝了硬木地板又鋪地毯的人
People who cover up their hardwood floors
一定活在裝修地獄里
deserve their own poorly decorated section of hell.
你看起來真像大人
Wow, you seem so grown up.
我是不是把舞袋留在你媽媽的車里了
Hey, did I leave my dance bag in your mom's car?
我不知道  有人可能知道哦
I don't know. You know who would know?
-她怎么會知道  -她對你了如指掌
- How would she know? - She knows everything about you.
我想她可以用"梅蘭妮尋回系統"
I figure she can use her Melanie LoJack System
徹底掌控某位傻瓜
and track that sucker right down.
這個  給你
Oh, here. For you,
給你  還有你
and you, and you.
-這是什么  -我正式邀請你們
- What's this? - I am officially inviting you
來參加我的喬遷派對
to my housewarming party.
抱歉  這么晚才給你們  不過我想
Sorry it's so last minute, but I thought heat and light
暖氣和燈光會讓聚會更歡樂的
would make it more festive.
我可以帶卡爾去嗎
Would it be okay if I bring Carl?
不行  都不準帶伴兒
No. No one brings anyone.
就我們四個
It's just the four of us.
不僅如此  我還邀請了其他人
Yes, and all the other people I'm inviting.
誰  你請了誰
Who? Who are you inviting?
淡定  班上的幾個女孩子
Well, freak, some girls from class,
米歇爾  我喜歡的三位同學
Michelle, the three people I like at school,
以及我的鄰居
and my neighbors
這樣他們就不會抱怨我們太吵了
so they can't complain about the noise.
你邀請科澤特了嗎
Are you inviting Cozette?
她和我們一起上課啊
Well, she's in our class.
-她來的話  就別算上我  -真的嗎
- If she comes, count me out. - Seriously?
-金妮  別這樣  -別怎樣
- Ginny, come on. - What come on?
四人成群  五人擁擠
Four's company. Five's a crowd.
好吧  如果金妮不去  我也不去
Fine. If Ginny's not going, I'm not going.
-你沒必要這樣做  -我樂意
- You don't have to do that. - I want to.
希望不是因為我
It's not on my account, I hope.
當然是因為你
Of course it's on your account.
-那就去啊  去  -不去
- Then go. Yes. - No.
我的天啊
Oh my god.
我們還沒正式做過自我介紹  我是薩莎
We haven't been properly introduced. I'm Sasha.
我本來打算邀請你
I was planning on inviting you
參加我的喬遷派對
to a housewarming party I'm having
互相了解一下對方
so we can get to know each other,
不過我那幾個朋友們
but my friends over there are re-enacting
正在重新演繹《返老還童》的后三分之一
the last third of "Benjamin Button"
馬上就演到四歲那部分了
and will soon turn four.
所以我們改天
So would it be okay if we just grabbed
去喝杯咖啡好嗎
a coffee sometime instead?
-酷斃  -我當你同意了
- Cool beans. - I'm interpreting that as a yes.
那就謝謝啦
So, thank you.
科澤特不去  行了嗎
No Cozette. Okay?
金科勒
Kim, Khloe?
此處指美國卡戴珊姐妹
為今晚休戰好嗎
Truce for the evening?
很好
Good.
那我帶卡爾去行嗎
So, do I get to bring Carl?
這是在沙漠舉辦的年度盛事
It's an annual event in the desert
慶祝自我表達的實現
that is a celebration of self-expression.
是嗎  有提到洗手間怎么樣嗎
Yeah, but what does it say about bathrooms?
看看這些圖片  天吶  太美了
Oh, look at these pictures. My god, it's beautiful.
好好好  有洗手間的圖片嗎
Yeah yeah yeah. Is there a picture of the bathrooms?
"公共生活實驗"
"An experiment in communal living."
我也做過  最終一條干凈毛巾都不剩
I've done that before. You wind up never having a clean towel.
那是什么
Ooh, what's that over there?
-一塊石頭  -我還以為是洗手間
- A rock. - Oh, I thought it was a bathroom.
你打算吃一堆路邊攤垃圾食品
Are you planning on eating a great deal of roadside food
然后一到那兒就開始翻江倒海嗎
and having some terrible reaction once you get there?
我只是害怕遠離洗手間  好嗎
I just have a thing about bathrooms, okay?
在方圓十英里內至少得有一個
I want one within a good 10-mile radius.
你是藝術家  得開放心態擁抱新事物
You're an artist. You need to be open to new things.
這就是我對伍德斯托克音樂節的感覺
That's how I felt about Woodstock.
你參加過伍德斯托克音樂節
You went to Woodstock?
我一開始不想去的
I didn't want to at first.
但這成為了我一輩子
But it turned out to be one of the best
最美好的經歷
experiences of my life.
因為我全身心投入了
Because I gave myself over to it.
那個溫暖  感傷又煙霧彌漫的周末
All I remember is this warm gooey haze of a weekend
充滿了愛和情感共鳴
filled with love and connection.
結束的時候
And at the end of it,
出現了個嬰兒
I wound up with a baby.
哈貝爾是在伍德斯托克被懷上的
Hubbell was conceived at Woodstock?
我沒在比喻  我離開時打開包一看
No, literally. I opened my bag as I was leaving
發現有人錯把嬰兒放進來了
and somebody had slipped a baby inside.
天哪  然后呢
Oh my god. What'd you do?
我把它留在停車場嬰兒丟失登記處
I just left it at the lost baby table in the parking lot.
那天有許多嬰兒被放錯包了
A lot of babies were put in the wrong purse that day.
伍德斯托克啊
Woodstock, huh?
洗手間環境怎么樣
What's the bathroom situation there?
-你好  -檢查一下你的信箱
- Hello? - Check your mailbox.
-它里面有東西在響嗎  -我寄了東西給你
- Is it ticking? - I put something in it for you.
-薩莎嗎  -對  向我保證你會檢查信箱
- Sasha? - Yes, just make sure you go and check
因為有時候你懶得查看
your mailbox because sometimes you don't.
你怎么知道
Why do you know about my mailbox?
因為有時候我們路過
Because sometimes we walk by
看到信件都滿出來了
and all the mail is spilling out
像是你永遠不檢查信箱
like you haven't checked it in forever,
我們懷疑你是不是掛了
And we wonder if you're dead,
不過沒人愿意進去看看
but no one wants to look.
萬一我需要幫助怎么辦
Hey, what if I need help?
如果你真掛了  那要幫也晚了
If you're dead, it's too late for help.
說得對  等等  五分鐘后就要彩排了
Good point. Wait a minute, rehearsal's in five minutes.
-所以呢  -你還沒到嗎
- So? - Aren't you here?
-不是吧  -怎么了
- Really? - What?
你還用得著打電話嗎
So you had to call?
你一轉眼就看到我了
You were gonna see me in three seconds.
我想請你參加我的喬遷派對
I wanted to invite you to my housewarming party.
你已經給我寄過邀請函了
But you already sent me an invitation.
沒錯  可你從不查郵箱
Yes, but you never check your mail,
誰知道你會不會看到
so who knows if you'd find it.
你打給我就是讓我查郵箱收信
You're calling to tell me to check my mail
所以我應該會收到的
to find it, so chances are I'll find it.
還記得我們藏在
Remember when we hid that
你包里的那串爛香蕉嗎
bunch of rotting bananas in your dance bag?
有這事  怪不得有股怪味道
You did? That's the smell?
去查你的郵箱
Check your box.
我看到一些照片哦
I found pictures.
簡直無法直視
Gah, must unsee.
在我看來像"永琲熄坏"那么刺眼
"Eternal sunshine" my mind.
你在維加斯待過  這有什么稀奇的
You lived in Vegas. How can this be shocking?
即使是在維加斯也會有人說
Okay, if that happened in Vegas, even Vegas would be saying,
"快來看啊  把他們趕出維加斯"
"Tell someone about this. Don't let it stay in Vegas."
伙伴們
Hey, partners.
米利  真是個驚喜啊
Milly, what a nice surprise.
我又帶來幾張支票
I just came by to drop off a couple more checks.
誰知道引座員的制服會這么貴
Who knew usher uniforms could be so expensive?
-是嗎  -難不成是羊駝毛做的
- Really? - What, are they made of vicuna or something?
我不知道是什么材料的
I don't know what they're made of,
不過看這價格  我自己都想
but at those prices, I'm gonna start
去做這生意了
selling them myself.
對于你的大力贊助
Just know how grateful we are to you
我們真是非常感激
for your patronage.
好了  各位  熱身結束
All right, everyone, finish warming up.
五分鐘后開始彩排
Rehearsal in five minutes.
范妮  我在想
Um, Fanny, I was wondering
-這會兒合不合適  -合適干什么
- if this might be a good time. - For what?
為我這個贊助人來一次彩排
Well, for my backer's rehearsal.
-你的什么  -我的贊助人彩排
- Your what? - My backer's rehearsal.
是為投資人準備的預先表演
It's a special advance performance for investors.
我們當然知道贊助人彩排是什么
Yeah, we know what a backer's rehearsal is.
-看來你看《節目單》 -什么
- So you read "Playbill"? - What?
《節目單》  我剛進商業圈的時候
"Playbill." I started reading it
就開始看這本雜志了  這么說吧
the minute I became a player in the biz, so to speak,
現在我簡直就是迷上了
and now I'm totally addicted.
你們知道《孟菲斯》的主演
Did you know the lead in "Memphis"
剛預定要拍一部情景喜劇嗎
just booked a sitcom?
-我們不知道  -是真的
- We did not know that. - It's true.
那么現在行嗎
So is now a good time?
反正你們現在也準備彩排了  那...
It seems like you're about ready to rehearse now anyhow, so...
米利  這絕對不...
Milly, this would absolutely not--
范妮  我能
Fanny, can I--
借一步說話嗎
over here for a sec.
她瘋了嗎
Is she out of her mind?
以她的名字命名露天劇場還不夠嗎
Isn't it enough I let her put her name on the amphitheater?
錯了  是命名藝術表演中心啊
Excuse me, on the performance center?
假裝我們是在看時間表
Pretend to be looking at our schedule.
藝術表演中心和劇院可不一樣
A performance center isn't a theater.
那是邁克爾·菲爾普斯訓練的地方
It's where Michael Phelps goes to train.
邁克爾·菲爾普斯 美國游泳巨星
-我知道  -那可是測試
- I know. - It's where they test
-昂貴德國跑車的地方  -說得對
- expensive German sports cars. - Don't disagree.
是男人名義上說去修車  實際上
It's where men with defective equipment have pumps installed
背著老婆去勾搭瑜伽教練的地方
so that they can leave their wives for a yoga teacher.
回到我們的話題上
Okay, come back to me here.
這是一種冒犯
This is an invasion.
她可以等到一切就緒以后再看表演
She can see the show when it's ready.
-和別人一樣  -這太吹毛求疵了
- Just like everyone else. - Okay, devil's advocate.
如果沒有米利  我們根本不會有劇場
If it weren't for Milly, we wouldn't have a theater,
或者燈光  服裝
or lights, or costumes.
更別說身材這么好的引座員了
And let's not forget the well-built ushers.
那確實是額外福利
That's definitely a perk.
她只是想看看彩排
She just wants to see a rehearsal
我們正好就要彩排
and we're already doing a rehearsal.
讓她觀賞一小段優美的舞蹈
Letting her watch a little pretty dancing
只是點小意思罷了
seems like a small price to pay.
好吧
Well...
告訴你個好消息
We have some good news.
我們查過了時間表
We checked our schedule,
應該現在就可以為你這位贊助人
and it looks like we can do your backer's rehearsal
-進行彩排表演  -真的嗎
- right now. - Really?
-真的  -太好了
- Really. - Great.
-只有一個小問題  -什么
- There's just one small problem. - What?
贊助人彩排
Well, backer's rehearsals
一般都要準備精美的食物
usually have beautiful spreads of food.
壽司拼盤  香檳酒
Sushi platters, champagne,
有一次我還見過有可麗餅的
one time I saw a crepe guy.
很遺憾因為通知得太倉促
It's just a shame that this is on such short notice.
-我們來不及準備  -等我打個電話
- We couldn't arrange that. - Let me make a call.
至少我們能吃好吃的
At least we're gonna eat.
你怎么在這兒
What are you doing here?
我想你不會相信
I don't suppose you'd believe
我是來報名的吧
I'm signing up for class?
喚醒我的巴里什尼科夫之魂
Channeling my inner Baryshnikov?
巴里什尼科夫 著名舞蹈家
不信
No.
其實我來這是想看看你
Then I guess I was hoping I'd run into you.
最近都沒怎么見你
I haven't seen you around lately.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
-我都忙暈了  -看出來了
- Things have been crazy. - I figured.
我是說  你的短信都不超過三個字
I mean, none of your texts are more than three letters long.
-抱歉  -有一半我都搞不懂
- Sorry. - I can't even figure out half of them.
"CTN"是什么意思
What does "CTN" Mean?
-現在沒法發短信  -好吧
- Can't text now. - Oh, of course.
視情況也可能是"現在沒法說話"
Or can't talk now depending on context.
你應該兩個意思都有
I think you've sent both.
真心抱歉  我最近生活一團糟
I'm really sorry. I've just been crazy with stuff, you know?
那你今晚忙嗎
Well, are you busy tonight?
-我在想  -今晚不行
- I was thinking... - I can't tonight.
-我  -行
- I'm... - yeah.
-好吧  -但我很快就能來找你
- Okay. - But we'll do something soon.
我保證
I promise.
我會發短信給你  這次四個字
I'll text you. Four letters this time.
米利  我們要開始了
So Milly, we'll be getting started in just a second.
-太激動人心了  -沒錯
- It's very exciting. - Oh, I know.
-大家都是  -你會很開心的
- For everyone. - And you'll be happy to know
我把硬糖包裝都拆了
I unwrapped my hard candy,
所以表演中不會有噪音干擾
so the noise won't be distracting during the performance.
我受寵若驚
I'm thrilled.
各位  今天的排練有位特殊來賓
Okay, class. We have a special guest for rehearsal today.
她是我們慷慨的贊助人  我們的天使
Our benevolent benefactor, our angel,
米利森特·斯通
Millicent Stone.
請叫我米利  當我不存在就行
Please, call me Milly and pretend I'm not here.
各就各位
Places, everyone.
從頭開始  然后蕾蕾的獨舞
We'll just run the opening, RayRay's solo,
最后是結尾
and then the ending.
-最需要加把勁的部分  -有道理
- Those need the most work anyhow. - Sounds.
她在干嘛
What is she doing?
音樂劇《歌廳》選段
慘不忍睹版的《我的先生們》嗎
A very poorly staged version of "Mein Herr"?
請放音樂
And music, please.
她不會...
She's not...
不是吧
No...
她在做筆記
She's taking notes.
-我要...  -別去
- I'm gonna... - No, you're not.
沒事的
It's okay.
大家跳得很好
Wonderful work, everyone.
非常非常好
Very very nice.
記住  下周三進行技術彩排
Now remember, we tech next Wednesday,
下周四進行服裝彩排
and dress on Thursday.
到時候見
I'll see you all then.
舞者們請到這里集中
Dancers to the chair, please.
她到底在說什么
What the hell is she talking about?
趕快  時間就是金錢
Let's go. Time is money.
什么事
Yes?
現在不行  我在做點評
Can't now. Have a note session.
好的  大部分跳得不錯
Okay, so a lot of good stuff here.
只有幾點不太行
Just a few things.
首先  奇怪你們怎么沒穿芭蕾舞裙
First off, it's very confusing that you're not wearing tutus.
人們去看芭蕾就是要看芭蕾舞裙的
People expect tutus when you go to the ballet.
-米利  -克制  克制
- Milly! - Back it up, back it up.
米利  這不是服裝彩排
Milly, it wasn't a dress rehearsal.
他們沒有穿戲服
They weren't in costume
因為這不是服裝彩排
Because it was not a dress rehearsal.
所以沒有盛裝打扮
So they weren't dressed.
我保證表演時會穿芭蕾舞裙的
I promise there will be tutus for the show.
很好  我們意見一致了
Oh. Oh, good. So we're on the same page.
很好  感謝你有益的建議
Great. So thank you for your helpful thoughts...
等一下
Hold on.
這個舞步太多了
There's too much of this step...
你是領舞  所以其他人就少跳點
You get the gist. So less of that for the whole group.
還有別轉來轉去的
And don't do the spinny thing.
我都看暈了
It makes me dizzy.
還有你  你有個動作
And you, you did this one move
看起來像是被絆倒了
where it looked like you were tripping.
其實就是我被絆倒了
That was when I tripped.
說得好  米利
Good catch, Milly.
你太對了  絆腳的動作得改掉
You're absolutely right. The tripping should change.
-對吧  范妮  -當然
- Right, fanny? - Sure.
有個問題  小矮人去哪了
And here's a question. Where are the dwarves?
小矮人
Dwarves?
我們演的是《睡美人》  得有小矮人啊
We're doing "Sleeping Beauty." There are supposed to be dwarves.
是《白雪公主》
In "Snow White."
小矮人是《白雪公主》里的角色
The dwarves are in "Snow White."
我們演的不是《睡美人和七個小矮人》
We are not doing "Sleeping Beauty And The Seven Dwarves."
我經常弄混
Oh, I always get those mixed up.
好的  下一條
Okay, next.
這么多鏡子是干嘛
What's with all the mirrors?
誰要一直看自己
Who needs to look at themselves that much?
好的  夠了  就這樣
All right. That's it. We're done.
等下  我還沒說完
Wait, I have more pages.
你想看排練
You wanted to see a rehearsal,
看也看了  到此為止
you saw it, we're done.
范妮
Look, Fanny,
《節目單》里不是說制作人可以點評的嗎
"Playbill" says a producer gets to give notes.
你不是制作人
You are not a producer.
我出的錢
I gave money.
制作人不就是給錢的人嗎
A producer is someone who gives money.
制作人有權發表看法
And a producer gets to have an opinion.
還有提出意見
And give notes.
而且他們還把刻有自己名字的椅子
And they usually have a chair with their name on it
我已經訂好了  周三前應該放到這
which I have ordered, and it should be here by Wednesday.
這就是當前藝術界的問題所在
And that is what is wrong with the arts today.
對藝術一竅不通的人
People with no knowledge at all
跟毒販子一樣在桌上扔一把錢
throw a wad of cash on the table like a drug dealer
大家就得言聽計從
and then everybody listens.
我這可不吃這一套
Well, not me and not here.
金牌電影制作人
你不是斯考特·魯丁
You are not Scott Rudin
這也不是約翰尼·德普的電影
and this is not a Johnny Depp movie.
這是我的工作室  我的作品
This is my studio and my production.
你絕對沒有權利評頭論足
And you have absolutely no right to give notes.
如果你有意見
And if that's a problem,
就寫封信給《節目單》
you can just write a letter to "Playbill"
和他們討論去吧
and work it out with them.
你們干嘛要聽她訓話
Why are you all listening to her?
你說她是我們的天使
You said she was our angel.
大家都出去吧
Everybody out.
所有人
Everybody!
如果你不采納我的提議
If you won't let me have my input,
那我要撤回投資
then I want my money back.
你明知道那些錢已經花掉了
You know that money's already spent.
我會起訴的
I'll sue.
那人們就會說你是那個
Then you'll just be known as that mean little woman
起訴鎮上芭蕾舞學校
that sued the town ballet school
毀了所有孩子夢想的吝嗇女人
and crushed all the children's dreams.
我才不管  如果你不信
I don't care. You can talk to
你可以去豪威爾的婦女中心打聽打聽
that Women's Center on Howell if you don't believe me.
現在那里變成干洗店了
They're a dry-cleaners now.
隨你  起訴吧
Fine! Sue!
現在就給律師打電話
Calling lawyers now.
呼叫律師
Call lawyers.
這有點...
Uh, so, that was kind of...
我知道
I know.
我們干嘛要帶這么多東西
I don't know why we are bringing all these.
這是個派對  人們都這么做
It's a party. It's what people do.
可派對的精髓在于
But the point of chips at a party
開懷暢飲
is to soak up booze.
這只是個16歲孩子舉辦的派對
This party's being thrown by a 16-year-old.
重點就在這  薩莎還是個孩子
That's just it. Sasha's a kid.
她可能準備的食物不夠
She won't have gotten enough food
然后派對無聊至極
and the party will suck
然后人人都會叫她瑪麗·理查茲
and everyone will call her Mary Richards.
上世紀70年代  美國情景喜劇女主角
被未婚夫拋棄自己一人打拼的女性形象
好吧  嘮叨老太婆
Yes, grandma. I'm sure all the kids
我肯定她會搞砸了
will be calling her Mary Richards.
我去拿面包做意式烤面包片
Hey, just getting bread for the bruschetta.
這是個16歲孩子的公寓
This is a 16-year-old's apartment?
或是奧茲仙境  簡直就是奧茲仙境
Or Oz. It could be Oz.
《綠葉仙蹤》中的奧茲仙境
-她還有壁爐  -還有柴火
- She's got a fireplace. - And wood.
有柴火在壁爐里燒
There's wood burning in the fireplace.
我在俄勒岡州住的時候  也有一個壁爐
I had a fireplace when I lived in Oregon.
有窩老鼠在那安家
The rats nested in it.
快看餐桌
Check out the food table.
她還有那種下面
Oh, she's got those metal containers
可以點蠟燭的金屬鍋
with the candle thingies under them.
那是小火鍋  她居然有小火鍋
Chafing dishes, she's got chafing dishes.
-勞駕  -什么事
- Excuse me? - Yes?
麻煩你給我找個靠枕
Could you please get me a pillow?
好的
Sure.
但別拿太好的
But don't take a nice one.
那我只能回我家給你拿了
Then I'll have to run back to my place.
去看看衛生間
Let's check out the bathroom.
她準許客人進去嗎
Does she let people go in there?
反正我要去
I'm going in.
我該現在加果仁嗎
Okay, now do I add the nuts?
瑪莎說蛋白充分打勻之后
Martha says when the egg white has been properly beaten,
碗底沒有明顯的液體殘留
no clear liquid should remain at the bottom of the bowl.
我沒看到明顯的液體殘留
I see no clear liquid.
-那就聽瑪莎的  -加入果仁
- Then follow Martha. - Adding the nuts.
水管沒問題
Pipes look good.
轉賣的時候能加不少價
That adds a lot of resale value.
在這別來房產中介那套  金妮
Take your broker's vest off, Ginny.
糟了  我忘了拿潘趣酒要加的冰環
Oh, shoot. I forgot the ice ring for the punch.
我來拿
Ooh, I'll get it.
好漂亮
It's so pretty.
那些三色堇是可食用的
The pansies are edible.
繡了名字的毛巾
Monogrammed towels.
她居然有繡了名字的毛巾
She has monogrammed towels.
-看到了  -不是應該要
- I saw. - Don't you need, like,
六周才能弄到繡有名字的東西嗎
six weeks to get something monogrammed?
不知道  我是用記號筆在內褲上寫名字
No idea. I write my name on my underpants with a sharpie.
那個不是你當啦啦隊長的朋友嗎
Hey, isn't that your cheerleading friend?
奧布麗  我根本沒請她
Aubrey. I didn't even invite her.
啦啦隊長能感應到有派對
Cheerleaders can sense parties.
天生的能力  她們還能
It's innate. It's like their ability
讓你覺得自己很卑微
to make people feel small.
薩莎
Sasha!
我不請自來不要緊吧
I hope it's okay that I came,
當我聽說我的朋友薩莎
'cause when I heard my friend Sasha
要舉辦派對  我覺得非來不可
was having a party, I just had to be here.
當然  朋友
Of course. Friend.
波  幫我照看一下
Oh, hey, Boo, will you stir for me?
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
你好  我是奧布麗
Hi, I'm Aubrey.
我是金妮  我們之前見過的
I'm Ginny. We've met before.
不可能
No.
-見過幾次  -沒有吧
- Several times. - I don't think so.
我們上同一節化學課
We're in the same chem class.
-你確定嗎  -我們是實驗搭檔
- Are you sure? - We're lab partners.
完全沒印象
Not ringing any bells.
-你好  奧布麗  -瑪蒂
- Hey, Aubrey! - Maddie, hi!
你怎么樣
How are you?
對她們而言  這就像呼吸一樣平常
It's like breathing to them.
你來啦
You made it.
-我們來了  -你就是那個16歲小屁孩
- We made it. - You're the 16-year-old?
那么兇干嘛
What's with the hostile tone?
我有點被刺激到了
I'm a little pissed by all this.
別理他  不過這地方好得沒話說
Ignore him. But still, this place.
還有家具  你還有水桶
And the furniture, and you have a bucket.
-必須的  -那可不一定
- Of course. - Not of course.
我就從來沒有水桶
I've never owned a bucket.
我也沒有  都是找人借的
I haven't either. You borrow buckets.
-懂我說的意思嗎  -別理他
- You know what I mean? - Ignore him.
是你先提水桶的
You brought up the bucket.
跟我來  帶你看點東西
Come on. I want to show you something.
這房間真漂亮
Wow. What a great room.
愛死這個梳妝臺和這些枕頭了
I love the dresser and the pillows.
還有嬌艷欲滴的鮮花和粉紅小青蛙
And how the fresh-cut flowers pick up the pink in the frog.
你早就進來過了  是吧
You've already been in here, haven't you?
當然
Totally.
所有東西都翻過了  內衣柜都沒放過
Went through your underwear drawer and everything.
你能教我怎么
Hey, can you show me how to do that thing
把襪子弄成一個個小球么
where you fold up your socks into tiny little balls?
這就是我想讓你看的
This is what I wanted you to see.
你從舞蹈教室偷來的嗎
Did you steal it from the studio?
當然不是  我專門請人裝上的
No. I had it put in.
在喬佛里芭蕾舞校  有個女孩告訴我
At Joffrey, there was this girl
她爸爸給她在房間里裝了扶手杠
who told me her dad put a barre in her room
讓她每天晚上都能練習
so she could practice every night,
而且她真跳得很好
and she was really good.
所以我想  要趕上她
So I figured if I'm gonna get that good,
我也要裝個扶手杠
I need a barre too.
好極了
Very nice.
看吧  我是認真的
See? Serious.
的確
You are.
看起來像是你會做的事
Seemed like something you would do.
你計劃好遭入室搶劫時的逃生路線了嗎
So, hey, do you have your home invasion escape plan set yet?
-那是什么  -這是我每搬進新地方
- What's that? - Ah, it's the first thing I do
都會做的第一件事
anytime I move in someplace new.
是單身女孩的居家必備
It's a total single girl must.
我會環顧房間四周  然后設想
See? I look around a room and I think
如果歹徒從正門進來
the home invader is coming in through the front door,
那我該躲哪呢
so where do I go?
絕對不能躲在衣柜里
You don't want to hide in the closet
因為歹徒一定會檢查衣柜
'cause he will check the closet
如果你被困在里面  很顯然
and then you're trapped, so obviously, you're,
你的小命就不保了
you know, see ya.
好?  你住在一樓
Now, you're on the first floor
這意味著你可以從窗戶跳出去
which means you can jump out the window
這好極了  但也意味著
which is awesome except it also means
歹徒可以從窗戶進來
the home invader can come in through the window.
所以你需要第二條逃生路線
which means you need a second escape route.
而且  你得祈禱來犯的不是一群歹徒
Plus, you hope it's not a group of home invaders
就像《即刻救援》里面演的  那...
like in "Taken", so...
法國驚悚動作片
不過我從沒遭到過襲擊
And nobody ever attacked me
平安無事  還撿到一只小貓咪
and I was safe and I got a kitten.
我們再去看看那個桶好了
Let's see that bucket again.
我把面包買來了
I got the bread.
失陪一下  別亂翻我的衣柜
Excuse me a second. Don't go through my closet.
也就是說衣柜里肯定有寶貝
That must mean there's something good in there.
好像看到某人的翻版喲
Well well well, somebody's got a mini-me.
少胡說八道
Stop.
看得出來她很崇拜[抬頭看]你
She totally looks up to you.
是啊  誰讓我那么高
Yeah, 'cause I'm eight feet tall.
我覺得這很有愛
I think it's cute.
但也有點危險
And a little dangerous.
-所以說你的吸塵機沒有塵袋  -沒有
- So your vacuum cleaner doesn't need bags.  - No.
無塵袋款性能更好  吸率更強
吸力也不會下降
And there's no loss of suction?
我用著覺得沒問題
None that I've noticed.
我去給你多加些冰
Here, let me get more ice for you.
我是奧布麗
Hi, I'm Aubrey.
-我是金妮  -真好
- Ginny. - Good for you.
-什么意思  -真希望我能像你一樣
- What? - I wish I could be one of those girls
大吃特吃毫不在乎身材
who just doesn't care.
等我有了自己的公寓
When I get an apartment,
我要把棖ㄗ磞邑礎
I'm gonna paint all the walls black
然后在天花板上掛滿銀色閃片
and hang silver tinsel from the ceiling.
-聽起來好嚇人  -怎么著也沒
- That's terrifying. - Not as terrifying
你的貴妃椅嚇人
as your fainting couch.
瑪莎說貴妃椅
Martha said a fainting couch is the perfect way
最利于采光
to create seating without blocking natural light.
她只是嫉妒罷了
She's just jealous.
我們都嫉妒得不行  你的公寓太贊了
We all are. This place is amazing.
我們絕對要把這當做我們的秘密基地
We should totally make it our hangout.
就像明妮·德瑞弗演胖子的
Like in that Irish movie
那部愛爾蘭電影一樣
where Minnie Driver is fat.
著名英國女演員
而且他們在樹林里還有家俱樂部
And they had that clubhouse in the woods
供他們開派對用
where they would all go for parties
還可以用作秘密幽會的地點
and secret trysts?
把這當作我們的愛爾蘭式秘密幽會基地吧
Yes, this could be our secret Irish trysty place.
沒問題  今晚留下來睡吧
Done. Hey, stay over tonight.
我們可以正式啟動俱樂部
we'll initiate the clubhouse.
-我恐怕不行  -我也是
- Oh, I can't. - Me either.
爸媽早就下了禁令
Parents shot the idea down.
但這是你的主意啊
It was your idea.
全程"無成人監護"活動
The whole "no adult supervision" thing
-是絕對禁止的  -沒錯  過界了
- is a no go. - Yeah, it was a big deal.
我們都發過毒誓
There was oath swearing and everything.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
但我們可以白天過來玩
But we can hang out during the day.
我們會想到對策的
And we'll work out a system eventually.
-明天見  -好  謝謝你們能來
- See you tomorrow? - Yes. Thanks for coming.
把剩菜帶回去吧
Take leftovers.
你們也要走了嗎
You guys going?
有段神秘的旅程等著我們呢
We have a mysterious something to get to.
-這派對很贊  -謝了
- It was a great party. - Thanks.
最后送你們個離別小禮物
Let me get you a favor.
-巧克力夾心甜餅  -還是熱的
- Chocolate chip. - And they're warm.
我的老天爺啊
Oh my god.
聽著  孩子
Listen, kid,
再給你一條建議
one more piece of advice.
別和隔壁的老太太混得太熟
Don't bond with the old lady next door.
-韋德梅爾奶奶  -如果看見她房門開著
- Mrs. Weidemeyer? - You see her door open,
立馬繞道走  而且無論如何
dive for cover. And whatever you do,
別告訴她你有車
do not tell her you have a car.
老太太都是奸詐的大騙子
Old ladies are giant con artists.
-騙子  -他們都是從些小事開始
- Con artists? - They start small.
讓你送她去集市或是毛線商店
Trips to the market and the yarn shop,
但沒一會你就會發現
but before you know it you're picking up
自己在晚上11點幫他們取處方藥
their prescriptions at 11:00 at night
并且在他們髖關節脫臼的時候
and driving them to the hospital
開車送他們去醫院  然后你覺得
when their hips break. And you think--
他們只有兩個髖關節  能脫臼幾次呢
they only have two hips, how many can they break?
答案是18次
18.
因為他們會一次又一次地脫臼
Because they break the same hips over and over.
明白了
Got it.
親愛的  我喉嚨有點干
Sweetie, my throat's a little dry.
你能幫我拿顆潤喉糖嗎
Could you get me a lozenge?
當然
Sure.
-那個女孩不正常  -我同意
- That girl is not normal. - I'm not disagreeing.
整個房間都沒有水煙槍
There wasn't a bong in the entire place.
我在她這個年紀時  房里只有水煙槍
When I was her age, everything in my room
剩下的全是能做成煙槍的東西
was either a bong or something I could make into a bong.
我25歲才擁有一臺電器
I was 25 before I owned an appliance.
是一臺用過的微波爐
It was a used microwave that had permanent
還沾有去不掉的湯漬  并且我很肯定
soup stains and I'm pretty sure
那臺微波爐輻射了我的卵巢
radiated my ovaries.
-我們該回去了  -對
- We should hit it. - Mmm.
記住  道路準則
So remember, rules of the road,
-別把你的座椅往后靠  -拜托
- no putting your seat back. - Come on.
-你會睡著的  -所以呢
- You'll fall asleep. - So?
所以你睡著了而我睡不著  這不公平
So it's not fair that you get to sleep and I don't.
如果你把座椅往后靠  你就會睡著
And if you put your seat back, you will go to sleep.
好吧  我跟你做個交易
All right, I'll make you a deal.
我保證我不睡著
I promise I won't fall asleep
如果你能保證車里有個廁所的話
if you promise me there's a bathroom at this thing.
行了  把你的座椅往后靠吧
Fine. Put your seat back.
你好  米利  很高興你能趕來
Hello, Milly. Glad you could make it.
謝謝你的邀請
Thank you for the invitation.
我可以幫你拿包嗎
May I take your purse?
干嘛
Why?
我只是覺得你把包放下會更加舒服
I just thought you'd be more comfortable without it.
-當真  -真的
- Really? - Really.
我拿著好了  謝謝
I'll keep it. Thank you.
我廚房的整修沒完沒了的
My kitchen remodel is taking forever.
所以我只能叫外賣
So I had to order in.
希望你喜歡布隆迪的菜
I hope you like Blondie's.
我挺喜歡他們的  他們按時交租
I do like them. They pay on time
而且沒有太多抱怨
and don't complain too much.
你還租給他們嗎
You rent to them too?
我的顧客名單是機密
My client list is confidential.
坐吧  米利
Have a seat, Milly.
要水嗎
Water?
水是生命之源
It's the staff of life.
我們自己動手  沒問題吧
Okay if we just serve ourselves?
我知道這不正式
It's informal, I know.
但這里不是唐頓莊園  對吧
But we're not sitting in Downton Abbey, are we?
沒錯
No.
絕對不是
Not by a long shot.
米利  咱們直入主題吧
I'll cut to the chase here, Milly.
早些時候我反應過激了
I overreacted earlier.
你試圖幫我拿包的時候嗎
When you tried to take my purse?
在贊助人彩排時
At the backer's rehearsal.
我同意
I agree.
但你要明白  是你把我逼到那份兒上的
But you have to understand, you forced me to act that way.
怎么說
How do you figure?
在創意活動上你的經驗不足
You haven't had a lot of experience with creative endeavors.
藝術創造不能民主
Creating art is not democratic.
這些胡蘿卜看起來不錯
These carrots look good.
我的舞蹈室是我的王國
My dance studio is my kingdom.
而我就是執政君主
And I am the reigning monarch,
我不習慣有人干預我
and I am not accustomed to input.
你可以創造一切你想要的
You can create all you want.
但如果你沒有一個舞臺去呈現
But if you don't have a stage to put it on,
那就是無用的
it's useless.
這上面是什么
What's on this?
-龍蒿  -好惡心
- Tarragon. - Yuck.
聽著  米利
Look, Milly,
我倆在這兒各自扮演著重要的角色
we each have a role here and they're both important,
但你踩過界了
but you stepped on mine.
當你握有財政大權時  就可以那么做
When you're the money person, you get to do that.
你可以踩在別人頭上嗎
You get to step on people?
外交上來說  是的
Diplomatically speaking.
沒有踩在別人頭上的外交方式
There's no diplomatic way to step on people.
這是你點的全部東西嗎
Is this all you ordered?
你總是對的  是嗎  米利
You're always right, is that it, Milly?
-你總是對的  -幾乎總是
- You're always right. - Close to always.
-真的嗎  -沒錯
- Really? - Yes.
知道什么是生命之源嗎  米利
Well, guess what the staff of life is, Milly.
不是水  而是面包
It's not water. It's bread.
我很肯定就是水
I'm pretty sure it's water.
-就是面包  -兩者都是
- It's bread. - It's both.
它們都很重要  人類缺水會死
They're both important. People die without water.
我們離題了
We're getting off the subject here.
是你先跑題的
You brought up bread.
為了我們合作關系的進行
For this partnership to work,
你需要做些讓步
you need to meet me halfway.
至少你能這么做
You can at least do that.
如果我不想  我就不做
Not if I don't want to.
順便問一下  你有面包嗎
By the way, do you have any bread?
瞧見沒  這就是沒人喜歡你的原因
See, this is why nobody likes you.
就是因為你的倔脾氣
This pig-headed stubbornness of yours.
不  大家不喜歡我的原因是我太富有了
No. The reason people don't like me is because I have money.
這不是大家不喜歡你的原因
That's not why people don't like you.
如果你明天就變成窮光蛋
If you lost all your money tomorrow,
人們還是會不喜歡你
people would still dislike you.
對  他們還是會不喜歡我
No. They would dislike me
因為他們嫉妒我有錢
because when I had money they were jealous.
沒人喜歡有錢的人
No one likes people with money.
他們喜歡沃倫·巴菲特[股神]
They like Warren Buffett.
饒了我吧
Give me a break.
他擁有喜詩糖果
The man owns See's Candy.
1972年巴菲特用2500萬美元收購了喜詩糖果
人人都喜歡喜詩糖果
Everyone likes See's Candy.
他們喜歡的是糖果  不是他
They like the candy, not the man.
只有他家人喜歡他
Only his family likes the man
因為等他死了他家人就能分錢了
because when the man dies they'll get money.
你想要什么  米利
What do you want, Milly?
你的底線是什么
What's the bottom line here?
底線嗎
Bottom line?
我受夠了只被人當作商人
I'm tired of being considered just a businessperson.
我希望在藝術方面被人重視
I want to be considered important in the arts.
這只是個小鎮上的小小芭蕾舞工作室
It's a ballet studio in a small town.
這只是個開頭
It's a starting point.
這需要了解很多事情的
There's a lot to know.
不是只要出錢就行的
It's not just about giving money.
我想了解所有的事情
Well, I want to know all there is.
如果有必要的話
If that's what it takes.
好吧
Fine.
那我會給你書  光盤
Then I will give you books, DVDs.
我會親自教你跳舞和芭蕾
I will personally teach you about dance and ballet.
我會讓我的鋼琴家
And I'll have my pianist
教你所有你想知道的關于音樂的東西
teach you everything you want to know about music.
怎么了
What?
聽起來是一場持久戰
Sounds mondo time-consuming.
絕對是場持久戰
It is mondo time-consuming.
這么問你吧  米利
Let me ask you this, Milly.
你是想了解藝術
Do you want to know the arts
還是只想看起來像了解藝術的人
or just be perceived as someone who knows the arts?
后者需要花多長時間
What kind of time commitment would the second one be?
-幾乎不用時間  -繼續
- Hardly any. - I'm listening.
我們做個交易吧
Let's make a deal.
我很樂意告訴任何你想告訴的人
I will gladly tell anyone you want
你是個藝術大師
that you are a master of the arts.
作為交換  你把創意主導權完全交給我
In exchange, you will leave the creative end completely to me.
怎么樣
What do you say?
范妮  我們交易達成
Fanny, I think we have a deal.
很好
Good.
你會告訴別人穿芭蕾舞裙是我的主意嗎
Will you tell people it was my idea to wear the tutus?
當然
Absolutely.
派對辦得不錯
It was a lovely party.
特別周到
So grown up.
老天哦  我都沒想到你夠年齡開車了
Heavens, I didn't even think you were old enough to have a car.
你有車嗎
Do you have a car?
沒有  沒車  全靠走的
Nope. No car. Just feet.
你好
Oh. Hey.
-你好  -你怎么在這
- Hey. - What are you doing here?
我聽說你在辦派對
I heard you were having a party.
對
Oh, yeah.
看來我的邀請函迷路了
Guess my invitation got lost?
我能進去嗎
So can I come in?
當然
Sure.
是誰告訴你的
Who told you about it?
奧布麗來我的比賽做啦啦隊
Aubrey was cheering at my game.
她以為我被邀請了
She assumed I was invited.
你什么時候又開始打籃球了
When did you start playing basketball again?
三周以前
Three weeks ago.
-這樣  -對
- Oh. - Yep.
離我們上次聊天好像有一陣子了
It's kind of been a while since we've talked.
我們現在在哪來著
So where are we anyway?
我的公寓里
My apartment.
你的什么
Your what?
我的公寓
My apartment.
那是個喬遷派對
It was a housewarming party.
你有了一個公寓卻沒有告訴我
You got an apartment and never told me.
一整個公寓  你真的搬家了嗎
A whole apartment. You actually moved?
是臨時決定的
It was sudden.
英國著名音樂家
所以如果我帶著手提音響到你家
So if I had shown up at your house with a boom box
大放彼得·蓋布瑞爾的音樂
and Peter Gabriel blasting...
新主人會報警的
The new owners would have called the police.
對  好的
Right. Okay.
明顯我們倆是沒有可能了  對嗎
So, clearly this isn't going to happen, right?
這不關你事  好嗎
Hey, this isn't about you. Okay?
我一直在處理一堆事情
I've been dealing with a lot of stuff.
我父母徹底地拋棄了我
My parents completely abandoned me.
我突然間只能靠自己了
I'm suddenly on my own,
我還要置辦家具  重新鋪地板
and I had to get furniture, and redo the floors,
我不知道你有沒有安裝過電器
and I don't know if you've ever set up utilities,
但是如果你沒有信用卡  就麻煩了
but if you don't have a credit card, it's a problem.
每次我想到我的公寓和你
And every time I thought about my apartment and you,
你跟我一起待在我的公寓里
and you in my apartment with me,
畫面就很奇怪很不和諧
it was weird and confusing.
我就想"怎么辦  他現在會不會覺得
And I'm like, "what? Is he gonna think
我在邀請他去一個沒有父母的性愛殿堂"
I'm inviting him over to my big parent free sex palace now?"
這都快讓我抓狂了
And it freaked me out.
而且我還要策劃派對  洗生菜
And I had a party to plan and lettuce to wash
所以我必須故意把你忽略掉
so I had to put you over there in a corner
因為我現在還沒法處理這事
because I just couldn't deal with it yet.
你比我想的還要奇怪
You're weirder than I thought.
而我以為你已經夠奇怪的了
And I thought you were pretty weird.
我為什么會以為
And why would I just assume
這里是"性愛殿堂"
that this is a sex palace, huh?
我連"性愛殿堂"是什么都不知道
I don't even know what the hell a sex palace is.
別理解錯了  那地方聽上去還不錯
Don't get me wrong, it doesn't sound like a bad thing,
但我不會只認為
but I wouldn't have just assumed
這是那種地方
that this is one of them.
-嘿  -干嘛
- Hey! - What?
然后呢
So what?
我們之間什么都不會發生了
This isn't gonna happen?
天啊  你有病啊
Oh my god, you're nuts.
你真是瘋了
You're seriously certifiable.
我一直在給你打電話發短信
I have been calling and texting
拋開自尊心
and throwing my self-respect out the window
可以說是在跟蹤你
and basically stalking you,
而你卻說我只比生菜重要
and you just told me I was outranked by lettuce.
所以沒錯  看起來
So yeah, it doesn't really seem like
你真的不想我們之間發生什么
you want this to happen.
-我想  -真的
- Well, I do. - Oh yeah?
-沒錯  -什么時候
- Yeah! - Fine. When?
-周五  -八點
- Friday. - 8:00?
-隨便  -很好
- Fine. - Great.
-再見  -再見
- Bye! - Bye!
那人怒了沒
Is the man on fire yet?
我們還沒到
We're not there.
你繼續睡吧
Go back to sleep.
這是在哪
Where are we?
稍微繞了個道  有點事情要處理
Took a little detour. Just have to run a quick errand.
我馬上回來
I'll be back in a second.
咋回事  我說讓你在車里待著
What? I told you to stay in the car.
我想買點薯條吃
I thought I'd get some fries.
我會給你買的  回車里待著
I'll get you fries. Go back to the car.
或者買別的東西配薯條吃
I might want something with my fries.
啥東西  你想買什么配薯條吃
What? What do you want with your fries?
不知道  更多薯條
I don't know. More fries?
回車里待著  我會給你帶
Go back to the car and I'll bring you
你喜歡的吃的
something you'll like.
到時會給你個驚喜  像游戲那樣
It'll be a surprise. Like a game.
-你喜歡游戲  -你好奇怪
- You like games. - You're being weird.
怎么回事  廁所里藏了槍還是咋了
What's going on? Is the gun behind the toilet or something?
你跟我開玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
-米歇爾  -你一路開車到
- Michelle... - You drove all the way to--
-這是哪  -薩克拉門托
- Where are we? - Sacramento.
薩克拉門托  薩克拉門托
Sacramento? Sacramento?
米歇爾  拜托  回車里等我
Please, Michelle, go back to the car.
史考特  告訴我  告訴我你為什么
Tell me, Scotty, tell me why you
開了二百英里的車來見媽媽
drove 200 miles to see mom.
一個我成功地躲了
A woman I've been actively successfully
12年半的女人
avoiding for 12 1/2 years?
這事與你無關  我就是要做點事情
This isn't about you. I just have to do something.
-做什么  -拜托
- What? - Please.
回車里待著
Go back to the car.
媽
Mom.
等一下
Hang on.
我趕時間  媽
I'm kind of in a hurry, mom.
如果我現在不看完這篇文章
If I don't finish this article now,
就得重新再看一遍
I'll have to start all over again.
你知道的
You know that.
天啊
God.
蘇珊·薩蘭登  美國著名演員
蘇珊·薩蘭登可真有趣
Susan Sarandon is so interesting.
應該多參與政治
Should have been more political.
參與政治的女人比不參與的
Women who are political are so much more interesting
更有趣
than women who are not.
你想喝點什么嗎
You want something to drink?
咖啡和薯條  謝謝
Coffee and fries, please.
-你在干嘛  -點咖啡和薯條
- What are you doing? - Ordering coffee and fries.
-為什么  -因為坐在餐館里
- Why? - 'Cause you can't sit in a diner
不點東西的話是超級無禮的
and not order anything. It's super rude.
回車里待著就好了
Just go back to the car.
別理我  就當我不在這兒
Ignore me. I'm not here.
-芝士漢堡好吃嗎  -看和什么相比
- How are the cheeseburgers? - Compared to what?
來一個芝士漢堡
I'll have a cheeseburger.
是米歇爾嗎
Is that Michelle?
是的
Yes.
你為什么帶米歇爾來
Why did you bring Michelle?
行了媽  開始吧  行不
Mom, please. Let's just do this, okay?
我沒準備好見米歇爾
I'm not prepared for Michelle.
我沒穿對衣服
I didn't dress for Michelle.
天啊  總之
God. Anyway,
我有說過公寓的事嗎
Did I tell you about the condo?
邊談邊看文件吧  媽
Talk and look, mom.
這套公寓非常適合我
Well, it's perfect for me.
有兩間臥室
It has two bedrooms
要是你來看我的話你就能住其中一間
so you can stay in one if you ever visit.
還有間房空出來我要把它變成錄音室
And a bonus room I'm going to turn into my recording studio.
她的錄音室
Her recording studio?
我告訴過你我要做張專輯
I told you I was gonna make an album, right?
她的錄音室
Her recording studio?
不  你沒說過  你不在這兒
No, you didn't. You're not here.
我一直想唱歌的
I always wanted to sing.
魯弗斯有專業工具
And Rufus has pro tools.
魯弗斯是我的新男友  這你沒問
Rufus is my new boyfriend. You didn't ask.
他更年輕  沒蘇珊·薩蘭登的男友年輕
He's younger. Not as young as Susan Sarandon's boyfriend,
不過他比我年輕
but he's younger than me.
太棒了
Well, great.
-你有  -他35歲
- You have the-- - He's 35.
我有個35歲的男友
I have a 35-year-old boyfriend.
是不是很神奇啊
Isn't that amazing?
一點都不
Not at all.
你知道什么有趣  海洋學
You know what's fun? Oceanography.
-啥  -沒什么
- What? - Nothing.
就是說  你要買套公寓
So, you're buying a condo.
沒錯
I am!
我朋友珍妮
My friend Jenny,
本來是她看中的房
she was looking at it first.
她想把空余的房間弄成健身房
She wanted to turn the bonus room into a gym,
不過作為錄音棚會更好
but it's gonna make a much better recording studio.
我想我該嘗試鄉村和西部風
I thought I'd try country and western
因為我戴帽子好看
because I look good in hats.
白癡的理由  是吧
Silly reason, right?
-是  -不是
- Yes. - No.
就是
Yes.
-你要的咖啡  -謝謝
- Here's your coffee. - Thank you.
謝謝
Thank you.
好陌生的詞
Those are unfamiliar words.
史考特  告訴仙妮亞·唐恩
Scotty, tell Shania Twain
美國鄉村音樂天后  諷刺她媽媽
專心看自己的文件
Eyes on her own paper.
媽媽  拜托
Mom, please.
哦對
Oh yes.
就是些法律條款什么的
It's just your standard legal blah blah blah.
我沒看見
I don't see where
監護人的名字應該簽在哪兒
the guardian's signature is supposed to go.
什么玩意
The what?
我想是簽在這
Right there, I think.
監護人簽名
The guardian's signature?
筆沒水了  你有筆嗎
My pen's dead. You got a pen?
喂喂  監護人簽名  什么監護人簽名
Hello? Guardian signature, what's a guardian signature?
史考特  史考特  史考特  史考特...
Scotty Scotty Scotty Scotty Scotty Scotty Scotty.
我是媽媽的監護人
I'm mom's guardian.
我得為她所有的財務交易簽字  好嗎
I have to sign all her financial transactions, okay?
我堅決不同意
How many ways can I say no?
聽著  她遇到麻煩了
Look, she got into a situation.
真嚇人
That's shocking.
她和男友買了房子
She bought a house with a boyfriend...
不是魯弗斯
Not Rufus.
他本該付一半錢的
And he was supposed to pay half,
可是他們分手了
but they broke up,
媽媽不想被房子纏住
and mom didn't want to get stuck with a house.
要擺脫唯一的辦法就是
But the only way to get her out of it
宣布她是無行為能力者
was to have her declared incompetent
這就需要我成為她的監護人
which involved me becoming her guardian.
你腦子進水了嗎
Are you out of your freaking mind?
拜托  別管這事
Please, just stay out of this.
你怎么讓她騙成這樣了
How did you let her con you into this?
她必須把房子賣了來買公寓
She had to get rid of the house in order to get the condo.
為了理解這里瘋狂的一切
I want to make sure I understand the full crazy here.
她宣布無行為能力
She had herself declared incompetent
就為了從一個住所脫身
to get out of a place to live
去住另一個地方
in order to get a different place to live.
她本來...
Well, she was supposed to...
等等  還沒到最瘋狂的呢
No. I haven't gotten to the crazy yet.
她為了從住處脫身
She had herself declared incompetent
假裝自己沒有行為能力
to get out of a place to live.
你還幫著她了
And you helped her!
她絕不能指望我住在那里
She certainly can't expect me to live,
那里有太多回憶
in a place with so many memories.
有誰明知道不能長相廝守
Who co-signs on a house
還和男友一起買房
with a guy they know it's not gonna work out with?
她不知道會分手
Well, she didn't know that.
從來沒長久過
It never works out.
和魯弗斯會的
It will with Rufus.
史考特  現在和我一起離開這里
Scotty, leave here with me right now.
先讓我簽了這個
Just let me sign this.
她會讓你惹上麻煩的
She will get you into trouble.
她一直在做這種事
'Cause that's what she does.
她把所有人拉進泥沼里
She drags everyone into her hole of destruction,
然后不知怎的她脫身了
then somehow she climbs out
-把你留在那里  -好生動
- and leaves you there. - So dramatic.
也許你該成為鄉村歌手
Maybe you should be the country singer.
媽媽給我打電話需要幫助
Mom called me and needed help.
那我該怎么做
What was I supposed to do?
經常換電話號碼
Change your number a lot.
我就是這么做的
That's what I do.
說得像我要打給她似的
She acts like I call her.
我才沒那么可憐呢  我有朋友
I'm not that desperate. I have friends.
我在錄制唱片
I'm making a record.
真搞不懂現在關她什么事
I don't see how it's any of her business anyhow.
她12年來從不關心
She hasn't cared for 12 years.
12年半
12 1/2.
我不明白現在就關她什么事了
I don't know why it matters to her now.
簽好了媽媽
There, mom.
拿著
Take it.
米歇爾
Michelle?
只是想看看你的臉
I just wanted to see your face.
上門服務
Well, door-to-door service
請給我小費
and I do accept gratuities.
你不可能永遠不和我說話
You can't freeze me out forever.
我可以
Yes, I can.
但是我不會
But I won't.
我該走了
I should get going.
下回結婚前先告訴我一聲
Give me some warning before you get married again.
通常情況下  不會過太久的
There's usually not that much time.
我明天再回自己家睡
I'll sleep at my place tomorrow.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
■
翻譯：paopao_mili 昕昕 依姍亦山
翻譯：袋小呆 silencelili 噎死青春
翻譯：包子萌豹子 salaph 無限彈
翻譯：H小欠 charcie 彤彤童鞋
校對：wendy妞 cindysheva End
后期：隨風飛翔  時間軸：Ans  總監：西之